{
    "subject": "resource/Ray_Musto",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Musto, Raphael J.",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Ray Musto is Musto, Raphael J.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9857708215713501,
            "question": "Is 'Raphael J' part of Ray Musto's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105422496795654,
            "question": "What is Ray Musto's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8972952961921692,
            "question": "What is the surname of Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8960400819778442,
            "question": "Is 'Ray' an official part of Ray Musto's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8306980133056641,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Ray Musto, what would you say his full name is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8156288862228394,
            "question": "Which name in Ray Musto's full name comes first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7684262990951538,
            "question": "How many names are included in Ray Musto's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7483533024787903,
            "question": "Does 'Musto' appear as a first or last name for Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6744958162307739,
            "question": "What are the first and middle names of Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190996170043945,
            "question": "What is the middle initial of Ray Musto?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Ray Musto is Musto, Raphael J.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5503_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the first and middle names of Ray Musto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5503_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'Musto' appear as a first or last name for Ray Musto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5503_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many names are included in Ray Musto's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5503_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5503_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information that confirms the triple statement. Specifically, the text mentions \"State Sen.  Raphael J. Musto\", which matches the full name of Ray Musto as stated in the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about a person named \"Raphael J. Musto,\" who holds the position of State Senator in Pennsylvania. Given that he uses the name \"Ray Musto\" in some contexts, and considering his full name is listed as \"Musto, Raphael J.\" in the provided context, the triple stating that Ray Musto's full name is Musto, Raphael J., is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}